(Episode 15)
Nothing has changed.
She is in a coma.
We're not sure at this moment
when she will wake up.
We'll have to see how she is tonight.
Eun Seo.
Jun Seo.
Answer me.
Jun Seo, answer me.
Please.
Please look at me.
Look at this.
She moved.
What?
Thank you.
Let me see.
Eun Seo.
It's strange.
It was moving.
She just moved her hands.
I swear.
Please don't be like this.
You have to be strong.
Let's wait a little longer.
She will wake up.
Eun Seo.
My baby.
Why are you breaking my heart?
My heart is torn to pieces.
You're breaking my heart.
Stop it. Why are you being like this?
I am afraid she might be
in a coma for a long time.
What do you mean?
Are you implying she may not wake up?
I cannot tell you anything for sure
at this moment.
She could wake up in several hours,
or tomorrow.
Or she might never wake up
until the last moment.
The last moment?
What do you mean by the "last moment?"
Tae Seok.
In her current condition,
even if she does wake up,
we cannot implement
a bone marrow transplant for her.
I mean, her cancer's still progressing
although she is in a coma,
so she could die...
while still in a coma.
She could die? Did you say she could die?
- Tae Seok.
- Say that again.
Tae Seok, what are you doing?
Get off of me. He said she could die.
She's not going to die.
What are you talking about?
How could Eun Seo die?
Why would my Eun Seo die?
Tae Seok.
Jun Seo, where are you...
Jun Seo.
Yoon Jun Seo.
Where are you going?
Eun Seo is here and dying.
Where are you going now?
Are you running away?
Are you running away? Are you?
When you said that...
I made you laugh. It was funny, so I...
It's open.
I think Jun Seo is here.
Yoon Jun Seo.
How is she?
When did you come, Jun Seo?
Jun Seo.
Have you eaten anything?
Would you like something to eat?
How is Eun Seo?
Has Eun Seo woken up?
I'm not sure.
Yes,
I will be out of the hotel for a while.
Yes, that's right.
It's much more important to me
than the hotel.
It is more important to me.
It is more important than anything else.
Yes.
Hello.
Are you really not coming to Eun Seo...
Hello, Ji Hwan. It's me.
Is Jun Seo there?
Pardon?
Jun Seo, no.
Don't do this.
Don't do it, Jun Seo.
I'm sorry.
You know what these are...
You know how much these mean to you.
Don't do this.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Let's go to the U.S.
Let's leave next week as planned.
I'm getting ready for that.
Jun Seo.
Where do you think you're going?
Jun Seo, look at me.
Are you going to leave Eun Seo
lying on her sick bed?
You knew it.
You were going to leave
although you knew, weren't you?
Nothing has changed.
We will go to the U.S.
Jun Seo.
I'm not brazen enough
to even ask for a breakup.
How can I possibly break up with you?
So you will have to break up with me.
If Eun Seo is gone, I know you can't live.
Then I'll die, too.
I can't live.
So,
you must break up with me now.
Please leave me.
Yes?
Let's go to the U.S.
If you won't go with me, I'll go alone.
Jun Seo.
- Here you are.
- Hello.
I'm here now, so you should get some rest.
I'm fine. You were up all night yesterday.
I slept in the morning.
I probably missed her so much.
I woke up early.
After I woke up,
I was dying to see her.
Please let me take care of Eun Seo.
Sure, of course.
Excuse me.
How you disappoint me.
You haven't even woken up.
I bought lots of food items
in case you ever woke up.
I guess I must eat them all by myself.
Are you jealous?
Whenever I come into your room,
do you know what I think,
and how absurd it is?
I imagine you're not here...
when I open the door to see you.
I imagine you have woken up...
and ran away with Jun Seo again.
It would break my heart again,
but now...
I think I can handle it.
I won't try to look for you.
I even actively hope you do that.
Could you?
Please.
There's no one but you, Tae Seok.
Please make Jun Seo stop.
He would listen to you.
Is he going to leave for the U.S.?
He said he was going to.
He said he would leave for the U.S.
and stop painting.
That is not like Jun Seo.
He can't do that. He's not himself.
Who is in their right mind now?
What if Jun Seo gave up?
What if he gave up on everything?
Tae Seok.
If that's what he wants, let him be.
Why is he giving up...
when Eun Seo hasn't given up?
Who does he think he is?
Tae Seok, please.
You're his best friend.
I know you care for Jun Seo
more than anyone.
What do you want from me?
I don't want anything anymore.
I think there are things we can't control,
no matter how hard we try.
Like Jun Seo and Eun Seo.
Shin Yu Mi.
Why are you, of all people, doing this?
Why are you being so cruel?
Do you want me to drag him...
and take him to Eun Seo?
Even if Eun Seo is in that condition,
how could I...
take Jun Seo to Eun Seo?
No.
I can't do that.
I won't do that.
I am...
the last man for Eun Seo.
Sin Ae.
What are you doing here?
Mom.
Did you see Eun Seo?
Sin Ae.
Has Jun Seo come?
Go to Jun Seo. Check on how he's doing.
And tell him to come here.
Why is he not coming?
Eun Seo is probably waiting for him.
I think I can understand him.
I don't want to see Eun Seo, either.
Sin Ae.
I think I'm the one
who should've had cancer.
I have always had this feeling.
I always don't feel right that
we got switched.
It was like I took everything
that belonged to her.
Why does she have cancer?
We shouldn't have gotten switched.
In that case, would I have had cancer?
I keep thinking about that.
It's a terrible thing to think that.
That's terrible.
You can't be like this as well, I...
Sin Ae, is Eun Seo going to wake up?
Of course, Mom.
You know how strong Eun Seo is.
Right.
You have such small hands.
Your hands look like mine.
You shouldn't have taken after
your dad's fate, but mine.
Then you wouldn't have had cancer.
No.
That's not all true.
Right.
You have taken after some of my fate, too.
That is why...
your life has been so unfortunate.
What do you want to be
if you were to be born again?
What about you?
I want to be...
I will be a tree.
A tree?
Yes, a tree.
Once it has taken root,
it can't move anywhere else.
I want to be such a tree.
Then I won't have to part with anyone
ever again.
What's going on?
What about her blood pressure?
What do you mean
her blood pressure has dropped?
What's happening?
I am sorry.
We have done everything we possibly could.
We are not sure whether
she can make it through the night.
She will be in her room soon.
Please prepare to say goodbye.
What do you mean by goodbye?
Goodbye to whom?
I am sorry.
Eun Seo.
Mom.
Eun Seo, Yoon Eun Seo.
She is your sister.
Isn't she cute?
Stay right here and wait for me.
I will be right back. Good boy.
- You idiot.
- Dad.
Get in a hurry to leave for the U.S.
Jun Seo being here is not helping Eun Seo.
Honey.
You don't deserve to meet Eun Seo.
Eun Seo.
I thought that would be
the best thing to do.
I've always thought about
what would be the best for our family.
I've always prioritized the best things
for everyone.
So, I've ignored how hurt you've been,
how much you sacrificed...
and everything you've been through.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Eun Seo.
I can't even say "goodbye" to you.
I can't do that.
Please forgive me.
You can't even push me away now.
I'll bring him.
I promise to bring him.
So, wait for me.
Let's go.
Let's go. Eun Seo is waiting for you.
Why are you doing this, Yoon Jun Seo?
Look at me, Yoon Jun Seo.
Jun Seo.
Eun Seo is waiting for you.
Let's go. Please.
Are you really doing this?
How can you do this to Eun Seo?
Let's go.
Get off of me.
- Get off of me.
- Let's go.
Get up and come with me.
- Get off of me.
- Let's go.
Get off of me.
Yoon Jun Seo.
Do you even know how I feel now?
This is the only thing...
All I can do is take you to Eun Seo.
The one thing that was allowed
to me as love is...
this thing here.
What she wants is always you.
Do you know how I feel?
Do you?
Tae Seok.
Do you know...
how I feel?
If I come,
I feel like she would be gone.
What if she becomes relieved to see me...
and then leaves?
If I were not to come,
would she keep waiting for me?
If I wouldn't show up to her,
would she live longer by waiting for me?
Tae Seok, I'm scared.
I'm scared to the point
of not knowing what to do.
Eun Seo.
Eun Seo, wake up.
It's Jun Seo.
I'm here.
So please wake up.
Even if waking up is...
more painful than sleeping like this,
please wake up for me.
I'm selfish,
but you always take me as I am.
You always wait for me.
You always forgive me.
So, wake up, Eun Seo.
Even if it hurts so much,
wake up for me.
I...
want to eat with you,
breathe with you,
and talk with you.
I want more time with you.
I want to tell you I love you.
Please don't take her away.
Please hear my prayer, anyone up there.
Please save my Eun Seo.
Please allow us a little more time.
A little more time.
Please.
Jun Seo.
Eun Seo.
Have you slept well?
I want to go home.
Eun Seo.
Eun Seo, we're home.
It's our first day.
What do you mean Eun Seo is not here?
Does it mean she woke up?
Did she?
I think she went out with Jun Seo
early in the morning.
Thank you.
Eun Seo.
Then what do we do now?
How will she be treated?
We cannot do the bone marrow transplant,
since it is too late.
So, I suggest that
she receives outpatient treatment.
Jun Seo.
Do you have anything to tell me?
What? Tell you what?
Don't you have anything to say?
I'm disappointed in you.
You promised to tell me that.
I'm not sure what that was.
You say it first.
No.
Then you won't hear it from me.
What?
Okay, then.
I can tell you that hundreds of times.
I love you, Eun Seo.
I love you.
I'll be good.
I'll be good to you.
I will try.
Will you marry me?
Give me one more chance.
No, I can't.
How can I ask you to do that
after all this?
I can't.
Are you all right, Eun Seo?
Jun Seo, go in.
Go in, Jun Seo.
Are you okay?
Go, Jun Seo.
Go in, Jun Seo.
I don't want you to see this.
Go.
Are you asleep, Eun Seo?
Yes.
Do you want to get more comfortable?
No.
I want to sleep like this.
Can't I?
Why not? Of course, you can.
Tell me something, Jun Seo.
I want to fall asleep listening to you.
What should I tell you?
Tell me what we're doing tomorrow.
Tomorrow?
First, I will wake up and clean up
for the first time in a long while.
Clean up?
I can't help you with that, then.
You can do what you are good at.
Rooting for me.
Okay. I will.
Then...
I will go to the college
to meet with the professor.
Don't take too long.
Okay.
What should we cook for lunch?
We'll think about that tomorrow.
Are you asleep, Eun Seo?
Yes.
Then I'll work on my project
in the afternoon,
and you should get some rest.
Will you?
And then in the evening...
Eun Seo.
Good night.
See you tomorrow.
Can you take a picture?
Tae Seok.
Why don't we take a picture
since you're here?
From the beginning to the end,
my life is all about you.
Promise me that
you won't think about dying, ever.
How can I live without you?
I'm very sick, aren't I?
I won't let you go alone.